<resources>
	<string name="app_name">Cairo City</string>
	
	<string name="category_coffee_shops">Coffee Shops</string>
	<string name="category_restaurants">Restaurants</string>
	<string name="category_kids_areas">Kids Areas</string>
	<string name="category_parks">Parks</string>
	<string name="category_shopping_centers">Shopping Centers</string>
	
	<string name="back_button">Navigate back</string>
	
	<string name="coffee_shop_name_1">El-Fishawi Cafe</string>
	<string name="coffee_shop_address_1">2 Al-Muski St, Al Muski, Cairo Governorate, Egypt</string>
	<string name="coffee_shop_description_1">
		Step back in time at the legendary El Fishawy Cafe. Established in 1920, this historic cafe is a true Cairene institution, frequented by artists, writers, and intellectuals for generations. The cafe retains its old-world charm with traditional wooden furniture, ornate mirrors, and shisha pipes hanging from the ceiling. While the menu is simple, featuring strong Turkish coffee and local karkadeh (hibiscus tea), the real draw is the atmosphere and the chance to experience a piece of Cairene history.
		Pros:
			Historic cafe with a unique and authentic atmosphere
			Strong Turkish coffee and traditional Egyptian drinks
			Convenient location in the bustling Khan el Khalili bazaar
			A great place to people-watch and soak up the local culture
		Cons:
			Limited seating, so be prepared to wait during peak hours
			Limited food options, mostly just snacks and pastries
			Smoking shisha is permitted, which may not be for everyone
	</string>
	<string name="coffee_shop_name_2">Osten Coffee Bar</string>
	<string name="coffee_shop_address_2">23 Hassan Assem St, Qasr ad-Nil, Cairo Governorate, Egypt</string>
	<string name="coffee_shop_description_2">
		Osten Coffee Bar is a contemporary space with a focus on high-quality coffee and a commitment to sustainability. Their beans are ethically sourced and roasted in-house, ensuring a fresh and flavorful cup. The menu offers a variety of espresso-based drinks, filter coffee, cold brew, and specialty lattes with unique flavor combinations. They also have a selection of teas, pastries, and light sandwiches.
		Pros:
			Stylish and modern cafe with a focus on ethically sourced coffee
			Variety of brewing methods and unique coffee creations
			Offers light food options to complement your coffee
			Multiple locations throughout Cairo
		Cons:
			Can be slightly pricier than some traditional coffee shops
			Limited seating at some locations, especially during peak hours
			May not have the same historic charm as some other cafes on this list
	</string>
	<string name="coffee_shop_name_3">The Jungle Cafe</string>
	<string name="coffee_shop_address_3">7 Sharia Emad El-Din, Azbakiya, Cairo Governorate, Egypt</string>
	<string name="coffee_shop_description_3">
		The Jungle Cafe offers a unique and immersive experience, transporting you to a lush rainforest environment. The cafe\'s interior is decorated with plants, vines, and even animal sculptures, creating a truly Instagrammable atmosphere. Beyond the ambiance, they offer a variety of coffee drinks, hot chocolate, teas, and a selection of cakes, pastries, and light meals.
		Pros:
			Unique jungle-themed decor perfect for nature lovers and photo enthusiasts
			Relaxing and visually stimulating atmosphere
			Variety of drinks and light food options
			Multiple locations across Cairo
		Cons:
			Coffee quality may not be the top priority for some, with the focus being on the theme
			Can get very crowded and noisy, especially on weekends
			Limited seating at some locations
	</string>
	<string name="coffee_shop_name_4">Cafe Corniche</string>
	<string name="coffee_shop_address_4">Semiramis InterContinental Cairo, Corniche El Nil, Cairo, Egypt</string>
	<string name="coffee_shop_description_4">
		Embrace the beauty of the Nile River with a visit to Cafe Corniche. This cafe boasts a stunning location along the Corniche, offering panoramic views of the Nile and the Cairo skyline. The outdoor terrace is the perfect spot to relax and enjoy a cup of coffee while taking in the scenery. They offer a standard selection of coffee drinks, teas, juices, and a variety of light snacks and desserts.
		Pros:
			Prime location on the Nile Corniche with breathtaking river views
			Relaxing outdoor seating perfect for enjoying the Cairo weather
			Standard coffee and tea options alongside light snacks
			Great place to people-watch and soak up the atmosphere
		Cons:
			Limited indoor seating, with the focus being on the outdoor terrace
			Coffee may not be as high-quality as some specialty cafes
			Can get crowded, especially during evenings and weekends
			Limited parking availability in the area
	</string>
	<string name="coffee_shop_name_5">Social Specialty Coffee</string>
	<string name="coffee_shop_address_5">Multiple locations across Cairo including The Nox and Leven Square in New Cairo</string>
	<string name="coffee_shop_description_5">
		Social Specialty Coffee is a community-oriented cafe that provides a welcoming space to work, socialize, or simply relax with a cup of coffee. Their menu features a variety of coffee drinks made with high-quality beans, alongside teas, cold brew, and a selection of pastries and light bites. They also offer free Wi-Fi and ample workspace, making it a popular spot for digital nomads and remote workers.
		Pros:
			Welcoming atmosphere perfect for work, socializing, or relaxation
			High-quality coffee beans and variety of brewing methods
			Free Wi-Fi and ample workspace for remote workers
			Multiple locations throughout Cairo
		Cons:
			Can get crowded during peak hours, especially if many people are using the workspace
			Limited parking availability at some locations
			May not have the same unique ambiance as some other cafes on this list
	</string>
	
	<string name="restaurant_name_1">Abou El Sid</string>
	<string name="restaurant_address_1">Several locations including Zamalek, Heliopolis, 6th of October and New Cairo.</string>
	<string name="restaurant_description_1">
		Abou El Sid is a local favorite, with a grand reputation for serving authentic Egyptian cuisine in a beautiful setting. This restaurant is especially known for its ornate, Arabian palace-inspired decor, transporting you to a bygone era. They have several branches across Cairo, but the Zamalek location is a top pick due to its reproduction of a typical 1930s Cairene house.
		Pros:
			Exceptional Egyptian cuisine in a beautiful setting
			Live entertainment adds to the ambiance (at some locations)
			Extensive menu with vegetarian options
		Cons:
			Can be expensive compared to other restaurants
			Reservations recommended to avoid waiting
			May not be ideal for a casual dining experience
	</string>
	<string name="restaurant_name_2">Koshary Abou Tarek</string>
	<string name="restaurant_address_2">Downtown Cairo</string>
	<string name="restaurant_description_2">
		No visit to Cairo is complete without trying a plate of koshari, Egypt\'s national dish. Koshary Abou Tarek is considered the gold standard for this comforting dish, made with layers of lentils, rice, macaroni, fried onions, and a spicy tomato sauce. This no-frills restaurant is a local favorite, and the portions are generous and very affordable.
		Pros:
			Legendary koshari - a must-try for any visitor to Cairo
			Super casual and inexpensive
			Always fresh ingredients
		Cons:
			Very small and basic restaurant with limited seating
			Limited menu (they mainly serve koshari)
	</string>
	<string name="restaurant_name_3">Zööba</string>
	<string name="restaurant_address_3">Multiple Locations including Zamalek, Maadi, Sheikh Zayed, Madinaty, Heliopolis, New Cairo.</string>
	<string name="restaurant_description_3">
		Zööba is a popular Egyptian chain that offers a fun and modern take on traditional street food. The menu includes all your favorites, like falafel, shawarma, and hawawshi, alongside innovative dishes like shrimp tempura and dynamite fries. Zööba is a great option for a casual meal or a quick bite.
		Pros:
			Fast, <casu></casu>al, and fun atmosphere
			Wide variety of Egyptian street food favorites
			Very affordable prices
		Cons:
			Can be crowded and noisy, especially during peak hours
			Not the most authentic Egyptian experience
	</string>
	<string name="restaurant_name_4">Naguib Mahfouz Restaurant &amp; Cafe</string>
	<string name="restaurant_address_4">Khan el Khalili (Old Cairo)</string>
	<string name="restaurant_description_4">
		Step back in time at the Naguib Mahfouz Restaurant &amp; Cafe, located in the heart of the historic Khan el Khalili bazaar. This charming cafe is named after Egypt\'s Nobel Prize-winning author, Naguib Mahfouz, who was a frequent visitor. The traditional menu features Egyptian staples like ful medames (fava beans), mulukhiya (stewed jute leaves), and umm ali (bread pudding). They also serve a strong cup of Turkish coffee and offer shisha pipes for those who want to relax and soak up the atmosphere.
		Pros:
			Located in a historic area, perfect for combining with sightseeing
			Traditional Egyptian food and drinks
			Charming ambiance with a literary connection
		Cons:
			Limited seating, so be prepared to wait
			May not be suitable for those who dislike cigarette smoke (due to shisha)
	</string>
	<string name="restaurant_name_5">Sobhy Kaber</string>
	<string name="restaurant_address_5">Downtown Cairo</string>
	<string name="restaurant_description_5">
		Another local favorite, Sobhy Kaber is a family-run restaurant that\'s been serving up delicious Egyptian fare for over 70 years. The menu is extensive, with everything from grilled meats and seafood to vegetarian options and homemade desserts. The atmosphere is warm and inviting, and the staff is friendly and attentive.
		Pros:
			Excellent quality Egyptian food at reasonable prices
			Large menu with something for everyone
			Warm and welcoming atmosphere
		Cons:
			Can get crowded, especially during lunch rush
			Limited parking availability in the area
	</string>
	
	<string name="kids_area_name_1">The International Children\'s Park</string>
	<string name="kids_area_address_1">Nasr City, Cairo Governorate</string>
	<string name="kids_area_description_1">
		This sprawling park is a wonderland for children of all ages. With a lake, a mini zoo, a variety of play areas, and even bumper cars, there\'s something to keep everyone busy for hours. The park also features a cultural center that hosts workshops and events throughout the year.
		Pros:
			Huge park with a variety of activities for all ages
			Affordable entrance fee
			Clean and well-maintained facilities
		Cons:
			Can get crowded, especially on weekends
			Limited food options inside the park, so pack some snacks
			Some rides may have a height restriction
	</string>
	<string name="kids_area_name_2">Galleria 40</string>
	<string name="kids_area_address_2">Located inside Arkan Plaza, Sheikh Zayed Road, Giza</string>
	<string name="kids_area_description_2">
		Galleria 40 is an edutainment center that combines fun and learning. The interactive exhibits cater to different age groups and cover a wide range of topics, from science and technology to history and art. There\'s also a dedicated play area for younger children and a cafe for parents to relax while the kids explore.
		Pros:
			Educational and entertaining exhibits for all ages
			Clean and air-conditioned environment
			Convenient location inside a shopping mall
		Cons:
			Entrance fee can be a bit pricey
			Limited free parking at the mall
			Can get crowded during peak hours
	</string>
	<string name="kids_area_name_3">Happy Land</string>
	<string name="kids_area_address_3">Several locations including Mall of Arabia, City Stars Mall, and American Plaza</string>
	<string name="kids_area_description_3">
		Happy Land is a popular indoor play area chain that offers a variety of climbing structures, slides, ball pits, and arcade games. It\'s a great option for a rainy day or when you need a break from the heat.
		Pros:
			Perfect for burning off energy in a safe and supervised environment
			Multiple locations throughout Cairo
			Ideal for younger children (toddlers to early elementary)
		Cons:
			Can be noisy and overwhelming for some children
			Entrance fee can vary depending on the location and playtime
			Limited seating for parents
	</string>
	<string name="kids_area_name_4">Kidzmondo Cairo</string>
	<string name="kids_area_address_4">Mall of Egypt, 6th of October City</string>
	<string name="kids_area_description_4">
		Kidzmondo Cairo is a unique edutainment concept that allows children to role-play different professions in a miniature city. Kids can try their hand at being firefighters, doctors, dentists, chefs, and more. It\'s a fantastic way for children to learn about different careers and develop new skills.
		Pros:
			Creative and engaging concept that allows for role-playing and learning
			Suitable for a wider age range (preschool to pre-teens)
			Offers a variety of role-playing options
		Cons:
			Located outside of central Cairo
			Can be expensive, especially for families with multiple children
			Reservations recommended, especially during weekends and holidays
	</string>
	<string name="kids_area_name_5">Al-Azhar Park</string>
	<string name="kids_area_address_5">Darb el-Labban, Cairo Governorate</string>
	<string name="kids_area_description_5">
		This sprawling green space is a great option for a relaxing afternoon with the family. The park offers plenty of space for kids to run around, a lake for pedal boating, and a small amusement park with a carousel and a few rides. There are also vendors selling snacks and drinks throughout the park.
		Pros:
			Free entry
			Large green space with plenty of room for kids to play
			Relaxing atmosphere and beautiful scenery
		Cons:
			Limited play equipment compared to dedicated play areas
			May not be ideal during very hot weather
			Limited parking availability
	</string>
	
	<string name="park_name_1">The Aquarium Grotto Garden</string>
	<string name="park_address_1">Salah Salem Street, Abbasiya, Cairo Governorate</string>
	<string name="park_description_1">This park is home to a unique aquarium built inside a natural cave system.
		Visitors can walk through the cave and marvel at a variety of fish and other aquatic life. The park also features a small zoo with animals like monkeys, birds, and reptiles. There\'s a botanical garden with a collection of plants from around the world.
		Pros:
			Offers a unique and educational experience, especially for children.
			Combines an aquarium, a zoo, and a botanical garden in one place.
			A great option for those looking for something different than the typical park experience.
		Cons:
			The aquarium and zoo might be smaller compared to dedicated facilities.
			Limited parking availability in the area.
			May not be ideal for those who dislike enclosed spaces (due to the cave setting of the aquarium).
	</string>
	<string name="park_name_2">Ain Al-Sira Lake Park</string>
	<string name="park_address_2">Old Cairo, near the historic Islamic Citadel</string>
	<string name="park_description_2">
		This scenic park surrounds a large artificial lake, offering a tranquil escape from the urban buzz. Ain Al-Sira is a popular spot for locals to relax, go for walks or jogs, and enjoy the scenic waterfront views. Visitors can rent paddleboats to explore the lake or simply unwind on the grassy areas. The park also features a small cafe and a playground for children.
		Pros:
			Scenic location with a lake and green areas.
			Peaceful atmosphere perfect for relaxation and enjoying nature.
			Offers opportunities for light exercise like walking, jogging, or paddle boating.
			Playground keeps children entertained.
		Cons:
			Limited facilities compared to some other parks on this list.
			Can get crowded, especially on weekends and holidays.
			Limited parking availability in the area.
	</string>
	<string name="park_name_3">Wadi Degla Protectorate</string>
	<string name="park_address_3">Just outside of Cairo on the Cairo-Ain Sukhna road</string>
	<string name="park_description_3">
		Venture slightly outside the city for a taste of desert adventure at Wadi Degla Protectorate. This scenic area features dramatic rock formations, desert landscapes, and hidden valleys waiting to be explored. Hiking, mountain biking, and rock climbing are popular activities here. The protectorate is also home to a rich variety of desert flora and fauna, making it a great spot for nature enthusiasts.
		Pros:
			Unique desert landscape offering opportunities for outdoor adventure activities.
			Variety of flora and fauna to observe.
			Escape from the crowded city center.
		Cons:
			Location outside Cairo requires transportation arrangements.
			Limited facilities; bring plenty of water and sun protection if you visit.
			Guided tours are recommended for safety and to learn more about the area\'s geology and ecology.
	</string>
	<string name="park_name_4">Giza Zoo</string>
	<string name="park_address_4">Giza, near the Pyramids</string>
	<string name="park_description_4">
		While not technically a national park, Giza Zoo is a historic Cairo institution that\'s a great option for families with children. Established in 1891, the zoo is home to a variety of animals from around the world, including lions, tigers, elephants, giraffes, and many more. Visitors can enjoy seeing the animals in their enclosures, take a ride on the zoo train, or grab a bite to eat at the on-site cafe.
		Pros:
			A great place to see a variety of animals, both local and exotic.
			Fun and educational activity for children.
			Convenient location near the Giza Pyramids.
		Cons:
			Can be crowded and noisy, especially on weekends.
			Some enclosures may appear outdated.
			Entrance fee can be pricey, especially for families.
	</string>
	<string name="park_name_5">The International Garden City</string>
	<string name="park_address_5">North Oba, Qalyubia Governorate (outside central Cairo, near the city of Obour)</string>
	<string name="park_description_5">
		The International Garden City isn\'t your typical park with benches and flowerbeds. This ambitious project reimagines urban spaces by focusing on sustainability, local food production, and creating a self-sufficient community.
		Pros:
			Unique Experience: Step into the future of sustainable urban living and witness innovative green architecture integrated with the community.
			Educational Value: Learn about urban agriculture techniques, renewable energy sources, and responsible environmental practices.
			Community Spirit: Connect with residents passionate about sustainability and explore a model for a greener future.
		Cons:
			Location: Further outside Cairo compared to other parks, requiring more planning for transportation (consider a day trip with a tour or hired car).
			Developing Project: As a relatively new project, some aspects might still be under development, and facilities might be limited.
			Limited Tourist Amenities: There might be limited restaurants or shops available within the community, so plan accordingly for snacks and drinks.
	</string>
	
	<string name="shopping_center_name_1">Citystars Heliopolis</string>
	<string name="shopping_center_address_1">Omar Ibn Al-Khattab, Heliopolis, Cairo Governorate 11771, Egypt</string>
	<string name="shopping_center_description_1">
		A true shopping behemoth, Citystars Heliopolis boasts over 750 stores, making it one of the largest malls in the Middle East. This upscale mall features a luxurious ambiance with international designer brands like Versace and Hugo Boss alongside popular mid-range stores. There\'s also a large Carrefour hypermarket, a cinema complex, a family entertainment center, and a variety of restaurants serving international cuisine.
		Pros:
			Extensive selection of stores catering to all tastes and budgets
			Luxurious ambiance and upscale shopping experience
			Family-friendly amenities like a cinema and entertainment center
			Convenient location in Heliopolis
		Cons:
			Can be overwhelming due to its sheer size
			Upscale stores may be on the pricier side
			Limited parking availability, especially during peak hours
	</string>
	<string name="shopping_center_name_2">Mall of Arabia</string>
	<string name="shopping_center_address_2">Beirut St, 6th of October City, Giza Governorate, Egypt</string>
	<string name="shopping_center_description_2">
		Holding the title of Egypt\'s largest mall, Mall of Arabia offers a staggering variety of shopping, dining, and entertainment options. This sprawling mall features over 1,000 stores, from international fashion brands and department stores to electronics shops and sports retailers. There\'s also a massive indoor theme park, a multiplex cinema, a bowling alley, and a vast food court with something for every taste bud.
		Pros:
			Unmatched selection of stores and entertainment options under one roof
			Something for everyone, from budget-conscious shoppers to luxury enthusiasts
			Family-friendly attractions like the theme park and bowling alley
			Ample parking space
		Cons:
			Located outside central Cairo, requiring transportation arrangements
			The sheer size can be overwhelming for some visitors
			Can get very crowded, especially on weekends and holidays
	</string>
	<string name="shopping_center_name_3">Cairo Festival City Mall</string>
	<string name="shopping_center_address_3">Fourth Settlement, New Cairo, Cairo Governorate, Egypt</string>
	<string name="shopping_center_description_3">
		Cairo Festival City Mall is a shopper\'s paradise, offering a vibrant mix of international and local brands. Think high-street favorites like H&amp;M and Zara alongside local boutiques and designer stores. The mall also boasts a large IKEA store, a Carrefour hypermarket, a multiplex cinema complex, and a variety of casual and fine-dining restaurants. Entertainment options include a bowling alley and a family entertainment center.
		Pros:
			Diverse selection of stores with a good mix of international and local brands
			Family-friendly entertainment options
			Convenient location in New Cairo
			Large IKEA store and Carrefour hypermarket for one-stop shopping
		Cons:
			Can be crowded, especially during weekends and holidays
			Parking can be a challenge, particularly during peak hours
			Limited luxury brand selection compared to some other malls on this list
	</string>
	<string name="shopping_center_name_4">Arkadia Mall</string>
	<string name="shopping_center_address_4">Mena El Nile Corniche, Ezbet El Nakhl, Cairo Governorate 11771, Egypt</string>
	<string name="shopping_center_description_4">
		Arkadia Mall offers a more relaxed and local shopping experience compared to the mega-malls. This multi-story mall features a mix of mid-range clothing stores, shoe shops, electronics retailers, and homeware stores. There\'s also a large food court with a variety of casual dining options, a cinema complex, and a children\'s play area.
		Pros:
			Relaxed atmosphere and a good mix of local and international brands
			Convenient location on the Nile Corniche with scenic views
			Family-friendly amenities like a food court and a play area
			Generally less crowded compared to some other malls
		Cons:
			Limited selection of high-end stores
			Smaller size compared to other malls on this list, with fewer entertainment options
			Parking can be limited, especially during peak hours
	</string>
	<string name="shopping_center_name_5">Ramses Mall</string>
	<string name="shopping_center_address_5">** 362J+GMW, Sahel Al Ghelel, Cairo Governorate, Egypt</string>
	<string name="shopping_center_description_5">
		A historic gem and a true Cairene landmark, Ramses Mall offers a unique shopping experience. Built in the 1930s in an Art Deco style, this historic gem and a true Cairene landmark, Ramses Mall offers a unique shopping experience. Built in the 1930s in an Art Deco style, this mall retains its old-world charm with ornate details and high ceilings. While not as extensive as some modern malls, Ramses Mall offers a good selection of clothing stores, souvenir shops, accessory shops, and a few restaurants serving Egyptian and international cuisine.  The highlight of the mall is the Ramses Hilton Cinema, one of the oldest cinemas in Cairo, showcasing a mix of mainstream and independent films.
		Pros:
			Unique historical building with beautiful Art Deco architecture
			Good selection of local and regional brands
			Convenient location in Downtown Cairo, close to the Egyptian Museum and Tahrir Square
			Houses the historic Ramses Hilton Cinema
		Cons:
			Limited variety of stores compared to modern malls
			Not a high-end shopping destination
			Can be crowded, especially during weekends and holidays
			Limited parking availability in the area
	</string>
</resources>