<resources>
	<string name="app_name">Month Of Cooking</string>
	<string name="recipe1">Tacos al Pastor</string>
	<string name="description1">This Mexican dish is made with thinly sliced pork that is marinated in a blend of spices and then grilled. It is typically served on corn tortillas with toppings like pineapple, cilantro, and onions.</string>
	<string name="recipe2">Chicken Tikka Masala</string>
	<string name="description2">This Indian dish is made with marinated chicken that is cooked in a creamy tomato sauce. It is typically served with basmati rice and naan bread.</string>
	<string name="recipe3">Pasta alla Norma</string>
	<string name="description3">This Sicilian dish is made with eggplant, tomatoes, ricotta salata cheese, and basil. It is typically served with grated Parmesan cheese.</string>
	<string name="recipe4">Pad Thai</string>
	<string name="description4">This Thai dish is made with rice noodles, eggs, shrimp, chicken, or tofu that are stir-fried in a sauce made with tamarind paste, fish sauce, and sugar. It is typically served with peanuts and cilantro.</string>
	<string name="recipe5">Lasagna</string>
	<string name="description5">This Italian dish is made with layers of pasta, meat sauce, and cheese. It is typically baked in the oven until the cheese is melted and bubbly.</string>
	<string name="recipe6">Beef Bourguignon</string>
	<string name="description6">This French dish is made with beef that is braised in red wine with carrots, onions, and mushrooms. It is typically served with mashed potatoes or noodles.</string>
	<string name="recipe7">Roast Chicken</string>
	<string name="description7">This classic dish is made with a whole chicken that is roasted in the oven until the skin is golden brown and the meat is cooked through. It is typically served with roasted vegetables or potatoes.</string>
	<string name="recipe8">Salmon with Roasted Vegetables</string>
	<string name="description8">This healthy dish is made with salmon that is roasted in the oven with vegetables like broccoli, carrots, and zucchini. It is a great way to get your daily dose of omega-3 fatty acids.</string>
	<string name="recipe9">Beef Tacos</string>
	<string name="description9">These easy-to-make tacos are made with ground beef that is seasoned with taco seasoning and then cooked in a skillet. They are typically served with toppings like lettuce, tomatoes, and sour cream.</string>
	<string name="recipe10">Chicken Stir-Fry</string>
	<string name="description10">This quick and easy dish is made with chicken that is stir-fried in a pan with vegetables like broccoli, carrots, and onions. It is a great way to get a healthy meal on the table in no time.</string>
	<string name="recipe11">Pizza</string>
	<string name="description11">This Italian classic is made with a dough that is topped with tomato sauce, cheese, and your favorite toppings. It is typically baked in the oven until the crust is golden brown and the cheese is melted and bubbly.</string>
	<string name="recipe12">Burgers</string>
	<string name="description12">These American favorites are made with ground beef that is seasoned with salt, pepper, and other spices. They are typically served on a bun with toppings like lettuce, tomatoes, and onions.</string>
	<string name="recipe13">Mac and Cheese</string>
	<string name="description13">This comfort food is made with macaroni noodles that are cooked in a cheese sauce. It is typically topped with bread crumbs and baked in the oven until the cheese is melted and bubbly.</string>
	<string name="recipe14">Fried Rice</string>
	<string name="description14">This Chinese dish is made with leftover rice that is stir-fried with vegetables and eggs. It is a great way to use up leftover rice and it is a quick and easy meal to make.</string>
	<string name="recipe15">Tuna Noodle Casserole</string>
	<string name="description15">This classic dish is made with tuna, noodles, cream of mushroom soup, and cheese. It is typically baked in the oven until the cheese is melted and bubbly.</string>
	<string name="recipe16">Chicken Pot Pie</string>
	<string name="description16">This hearty dish is made with chicken, vegetables, and a flaky crust. It is typically baked in the oven until the crust is golden brown.</string>
	<string name="recipe17">Lasagna Soup</string>
	<string name="description17">This comforting soup is made with layers of lasagna noodles, meat sauce, and cheese. It is a great way to enjoy lasagna without all the work.</string>
	<string name="recipe18">Beef Chili</string>
	<string name="description18">This hearty chili is made with ground beef, beans, tomatoes, and spices. It is typically served with cornbread or rice.</string>
	<string name="recipe19">Beef Stroganoff</string>
	<string name="description19">This classic Russian dish is made with beef that is cooked in a creamy mushroom sauce and served over noodles. It is a hearty and satisfying dish that is perfect for a cold winter night.</string>
	<string name="recipe20">Vegetarian Chili</string>
	<string name="description20">This vegan chili is made with beans, corn, tomatoes, and spices. It is a great option for vegetarians and vegans.</string>
	<string name="recipe21">Beef Stew</string>
	<string name="description21">This classic dish is made with beef that is braised in a broth with vegetables like carrots, potatoes, and onions. It is typically served with crusty bread.</string>
	<string name="recipe22">Chicken Stew</string>
	<string name="description22">This hearty stew is made with chicken, vegetables, and a creamy sauce. It is a great way to warm up on a cold day.</string>
	<string name="recipe23">Pot Roast</string>
	<string name="description23">This classic dish is made with a beef roast that is cooked in a slow cooker with vegetables and spices. It is a great way to have a delicious and easy meal ready when you get home from work.</string>
	<string name="recipe24">Grilled Salmon</string>
	<string name="description24">This healthy and delicious dish is made with salmon that is grilled to perfection. It is a great way to get your daily dose of omega-3 fatty acids.</string>
	<string name="recipe25">Grilled Chicken Breasts</string>
	<string name="description25">These easy-to-make chicken breasts are grilled to perfection. They are a great source of protein and can be served with a variety of sides.</string>
	<string name="recipe26">Grilled Shrimp</string>
	<string name="description26">This quick and easy dish is made with shrimp that are grilled to perfection. They are a great source of protein and can be served with a variety of sides.</string>
	<string name="recipe27">Shrimp Scampi</string>
	<string name="description27">This classic Italian dish is made with shrimp that are cooked in a garlicky white wine sauce. It is typically served over pasta.</string>
	<string name="recipe28">Risotto</string>
	<string name="description28">This Italian rice dish is made with arborio rice that is cooked in a broth with vegetables and cheese. It is a hearty and satisfying dish.</string>
	<string name="recipe29">Paella</string>
	<string name="description29">This Spanish rice dish is made with saffron rice that is cooked with seafood, chicken, and vegetables. It is a flavorful and colorful dish.</string>
	<string name="recipe30">Tiramisu</string>
	<string name="description30">This Italian dessert is made with ladyfingers that are soaked in coffee and layered with a creamy mascarpone cheese mixture. It is a decadent and delicious treat.</string>
</resources>